A Guide to the Purnell W. Choppin papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA151
Rockefeller Archive Center
Purnell W. Choppin papers, Rockefeller University Faculty
circa 1958-1986, Bulk: 1970-1985
bulk
Rockefeller Archive Center
Choppin, Purnell W.
Rockefeller University
Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
FA151
29 Box(es) Extent is approximate.
Biographical/Historical note
Purnell W. Choppin (1929- ) an animal virologist, came to Rockefeller University and hospital in 1957 under a fellowship from the National Foundation. For twenty eight years Dr. Choppin's research was primarily concerned with the influenza and parainfluenza viruses. His papers consist of lab. notebooks, reports minutes, of meetings, printed materials, lectures, memoranda and correspondence. In 1970 he was appointed professor and senior physician and served as vice president for academic program (1983).
Choppin was born on July 4, 1929 in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, and attended Louisiana State University where he received an M.D. degree from its School of Medicine in 1953.
Professor Choppin served in an advisory capacity to several scientific organizations; the NIAID's influenza Commision, Markey Scholars Program and as chairman of the Virology Study Section of the National Institute of Health.
In 1983 Dr. Choppin received the Howard Taylor Rickett Award of the University of Chicago. Currently, he is the Chairman of the Virology Department at the Howard Hughes Institute in New York.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into 3 components:
Laboratory Notebooks (Box 1-6).
Series 1: Meetings, Seminars and Workshops (Box 7-27).
Series 2: Markey Scholars Program (Box 28-29).
Arrangement note
Series 1 and Series 2 are arranged in alphabetical order then in chronological order within subjects.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be closed to research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment
Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be closed to researchers at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/Head of Reference.
File Plan note
Former Classification: I 450 C455
Conditions Governing Access note
Limited access; consult archivist.
Biology -- Research; Medical research; Viruses -- Research; Immunology; Choppin, Purnell W.; Rockefeller University; Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
- Laboratory Notebooks, 1960-1973; 6 boxes
  - Laboratory notebooks (Box 1)
  - Laboratory notebooks (Box 2)
  - Laboratory notebooks (Box 3)
  - Laboratory notebooks (Box 4)
  - Laboratory notebooks (Box 5)
  - Laboratory notebooks (Box 6)
- Meetings, Seminars, and Workshops, 1958-1985; 1
  Arrangement
  Series 1 and Series 2 are arranged in alphabetical order then in chronological order within subjects.
  - AAAS Demonstrations, 1967 December (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Acoms Lecture, 6/9/1984 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - ACS Science Writers, 4/2-5/1971 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Acute Respiratory Diseases Symposium, 3/9/1973 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Acyclovir Meeting NIH Meeting, 9/9-11/1981 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Antiviral Workshop Planning, 5/26/02 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Antiviral Workshop NIH, 12/12-13/1974 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Antivirals NY Hospital-Cornell RU Meeting, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - American Cancer Meeting, 9/15-16/1983 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - American Cancer Society Meeting, 9/13-14/1984 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - American Cancer Society Council Meeting, 4/12-13/1984 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - American Cancer Society Council, 4/7-8/1983 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - American Clinical & Climatological Association, 1975-1985 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - American Society for Cell Biology, 11/29/1983 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - American Society for Cell Biology San Diego, 11/20-23/1974 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - American Society for Clinical Investigation, 1983-1985 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - American Society of Biological Chemists, 6/16/1971 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - American Society of Virology Meeting, 7/10-14/1983 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - American Society of Virology Meeting Ithaca, 8/2-5/1982 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - ASCI Meeting, 5/2-3/1971 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - ASM Lectures, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - ASM Meeting, 3/4-8/1984 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - ASM Meeting New Orleans, 3/7-10/1983 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - ASM Meeting Honolulu, 5/8-11/1979 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - ASM Meeting, 5/14-19/1978 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - ASM Meeting, 5/10-17/1974 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - ASM Meeting, 4/23-28/1972 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - ASM Meeting Boston 4/26 & 5/1/1970 Klenk Friday Talk 4/29/1970 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - ASM Meeting Minneapolis, 5/2-7/1971 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Association of American Physicians, 1979-1985 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - ASV Meeting Albuquerque, 7/21/1985 7/25/1985 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - ASV Meeting, 8/9-14/1987 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Baylor Seminar Houston, 11/12/1974 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Berlin Workshop 1/17-18/1973 PHRI Talk 12/12/1972, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Biotechnology Meeting LSU New Orleans, 12/12/1984 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Book-Pagano, 1974-1982 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - BRLA Talk, 10/9/1965 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - California Membrane Conference, 3/13-17/1972 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Campione Visiting Lecturer Northwestern, 3/27/1984 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Cancer Panel, 6/3/1985 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Caspary Lecture, 1/4/1974 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Cell Biology Meeting, 10/1980 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Cell-Cell Interactions La Jolla, 2/6-9/1978 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Cell Biology Meeting, 11/4-8/1978 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Cellular Interactions Symposium Minneapolis, 5/6-8/1981 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - CIASC, 10/18/1985 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - CIBA Foundation Symposium, 5/11/1980 5/18/1980 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Chicago & St. Louis, 4/6-7/1981 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Charismas Lectures, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Cold Spring Harbor, 5/22-27/1979 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Cold Spring Harbor, 1972 1974 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Cold Spring Harbor, 1967 August (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Cold Spring Harbor, 1968-1970 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Colloquium Abstracts, 1964-1970 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Colloquium-Problem of Antiviral Therapy England, 9/1982 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Columbia Seminar 1/23/1968 Yale 2/9/1960 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Duke University, 1/28/1971 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Du Pont Seminar 10/1969 Immunological Disorders of Nervous 12/5-6/1969 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - VIII International Congress for Microbiology, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Emery Medical School Review Committee, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - EPA Virology Meeting, 11/1/1984 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Federation Meeting St. Louis, 4/3/1984 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Federation Meeting University of South Dakota, 4/12-17/1970 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Federation 1960 ASM 1968, 1960-1968 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Federation Chicago 1967 ASM New York 1967 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Federation 1965 Colorado Meeting 1965 Interurban 1965 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Federation of European Biochemical Societies Helsinki, 8/9-14/1970 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Federation Proceeding 1963 Wed. Talk 1963 ASM 1963 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - 1st International Virology Congress, [1968] (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 5th International Congress of Virology, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Florida M.O. Anderson, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 4th International Virology Congress The Hague, 8/30/1978-9/6/1978 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Frontispiece (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Gordon Conference, 1973; 1 of 2 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Gordon Conference, 1973; 2 of 2 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Gordon Conference, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Gordon Conference, 8/30/1971 9/4/1971 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Gordon Conference, 7/28/1969 8/1/1969 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Gordon Conference, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Gordon Conference, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Gordon Conference, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Gordon Conference, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Gordon Conference, 6/20-24/1977 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Gustav Stern Symposium Perspectives on Virology, 2/4-5/1980 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Gustav Stern Perspective in Virology, 2/4-5/1974 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Gustav Stern Conference Foot & Mouth Disease, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Harvey Lecture, 5/16/1985 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Hershey Lectures Federation Lab. Visit, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Hodes Symposium, 6/4/1981 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Immunology Study Section, 6/10-21/1978 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Infectious Diseases Society Meeting, 9/25/1980 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Infectious Diseases Society Meeting & NYU, 9/26/1972 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - influenza B Workshop, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Influenza Center Site Visit Houston, 4/18-19/1979 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Influenza Meeting Canberra, 12/10-12/1979 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Influenza Subcommittee, 10/11-12/1973 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Influenza Symposium Salt Lake City, 3/8-13/1981 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Influenza Steering Group, 10/23/1974 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Influenza Vaccine Meeting New, 2/7/1977 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Influenza Virus Hemagglutinin Meeting Vienna 3/21-22/1972, 1972-1984 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Influenza Workshop Seattle, 5/20-21/1974; 1 of 2 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Influenza Workshop Seattle, 5/20-21/1974; 2 of 2 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - IGN UCLA Symposium Keystone Colorado, 3/9/1980 3/14/1980 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - International Conference Biological Membranes, 6/10-16/1973 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - International Congress Pharmacology London, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - IOM and IDSA Mooting, 10/10-11/1984 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Iran, 1975; 1 of 3 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Iran, 1975; 2 of 3 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Iran, 1975; 3 of 3 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Japan Conference, 12/1968 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Jefferson Medical College Lecture, 11/29/1983 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Jefferson 1968 Meharry Medical College, 10/27/1967 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Johns Hopkins Lecture, 10/22/1980 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Johns Hopkins Seminar, 12/5/1984 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Journal Club, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Kinyoun Lecture, 10/9/1979 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - London Colloquium of Influenza, 9/21/1983 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - LSU Alumni. Award, 10/13/1983 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - LSU, 4/16-18/1978 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Macy Receptor Conference, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - McGill University 02/1972 University of Alabama, 3/28/1972 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - McMaster University Hamilton Ontario, 12/12/1978 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Mechanisms of Viral Persistence Aspen Colorado, (6/7-8/1980) (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Medac Meating Amsterdam, 6/14-17/1981 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Meeting Belfast Northern Ireland, 4/9-10/1974 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Meetings & Workshops, 1976; 1 of 3 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Meetings & Workshops, 1976; 2 of 3 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Meetings & Workshops, 1976; 3 of 3 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Meetings & Workshops, 1975; 1 of 3 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Meetings & Workshops, 1975; 2 of 3 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Meetings & Workshops, 1975; 3 of 3 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Merk Institute Seminar, 1/21/1980 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Miles Symposium, 6/24-25/1974 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - MID Committee Bethesda, 6/29/1982 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - MIT Seminar, 4/1/1980 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Montifiore Hospital Grand Round 2/17/1982 Stony Brook 12/17/1981 Pas 10/4/1981 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Morden Approaches of Vaccine Cold Spring Harbor, 9/12-16/1984 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Mount Sinai Medical School, 2/21/1973 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Multiple Sclerosis Clinical Center, 1970-1979 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - MS Advisory Committee Meeting, 4/5/1982 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - MS Advisory Council Meeting, 10/10/1980 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - MS Committee, 4/4/1981 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - MS Committee, 10/15/1982 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - MS Meeting, 4/22/1983 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - MS Meeting, 10/21/1983 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - MS Meeting, 10/15/1982 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - MS Meeting, 3/28/1980 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - MS Meeting University of West Ontario, 5/3-5/1981 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - MS Meeting Woods Hole, 4/7-10/1983 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - MS Society Meeting, 10/23/1981 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - MS Society Meeting, 4/7/1984 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - MS Society Meeting, 10/26/1984 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Myxovirus Genetics Meeting, 3/6-8/1977 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - NAS Meeting, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - NAS Meeting, 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - NAS Members, 1977-1982 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - National Multiple Sclerosis Society Advisory Committee, 3/30/1979 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - NATO Course Les Arcs France, 6/19-7/2/1983 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Negative Strand Viruses Cambridge, 8/15-21/1985 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Negative Strand Viruses Cambridge, 8/1-5/1977 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Negative Strand Viruses Cambridge, 7/1973 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Neurosciences Research, 1/31/1972 2/1/1972 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - NFIP Fellowship, 1957-1961 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - NIH 4/1969 Princeton 6/1969 Comparative Virology Montreal (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - NIH RSV Parainfluenza Virus Workshop, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - NY Academy of Science Conference, 11/28-30/1978 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - New York Hospital, 2/16/1971 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - NYAM 10/12/1967 MIT 11/22/1967 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - NYAS Lecture, 2/20/1985 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - NIAID Council, 5/22/1979 5/24/1979 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - NIAID Council, 1/24-26/1979; 1 of 2 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - NIAID Council, 1/24-26/1979; 2 of 2 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - NIAID Council, 1/29-30/1981; 1 of 3 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - NIAID Council, 1/29-30/1901; 2 of 3 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - NIAID Council, 1/29-30/1901; 3 of 3 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - NIAID Council, 9/24-25/1981 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - NIAID Council, 1/28-29/1982 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - NIAID Council, 5/27-28/1982 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - NIAID Council, 1/27-28/1983; 1 of 2 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - NIAID Council, 1/27-20/1983; 2 of 2 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - NIAID Council, 5/23-24/1983 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - NIAID Council, 9/22-23/1983 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - NIAID Council Meeting, 1/24/1985 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - NIAID Council Meeting, 1/26-27/1984 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - NIAID Council Meeting, 9/23-24/1982; 1 of 3 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - NIAID Council Meeting, 9/23-24/1982; 2 of 3 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - NIAID Council Meeting, 9/23-24/1982; 3 of 3 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - NIAID Council Meeting, 9/28/1980 10/1/1980 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - NIAID Council Meeting, 5/22-23/1980; 1 of 3 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - NIAID Council Meeting, 5/22-23/1980; 2 of 3 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - NIAID Council Meeting, 5/22-23/1980; 3 of 3 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - NIAID Council Meeting, 1/31/1980 2/1/1980; 1 of 3 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - NIAID Council Meeting, 1/31/1980 2/1/1980; 2 of 3 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - NIAID Council Meeting, 1/31/1980 2/1/1980; 3 of 3 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - NIAID Council Meeting, 5/28-29/1981 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - NIAID Council Meeting, 10/22-24/1979 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - NIAID Council Report, 1/27-28/1983 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - NIAID Director's Report to Council, 1984 January (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - NIAID Postdoctoral Training, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - NIAID Workshop on Influenza Vaccine, 12/10-11/1984 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - NSF Meeting, 12/10-11/1971 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - NSF Reviews, [1976-1982]; 1 of 3 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - NSF Reviews, [1976-1982]; 2 of 3 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - NSF Reviews, 1976-1982; 3 of 3 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Oholo Conference Israel, 3/1983 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Origin of Pandemic Influenza Viruses Peking, 11/10/1982 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Paramyxovirus Study Group (ICTV), 1976-1984; 1 of 3 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Paramyxovirus Study Group (ICTV), 1904-1976; 2 of 3 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Paramyxovirus Study Group (ICTV), 1976-1984; 3 of 3 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Paramyxoviruses (Book), 1903-1984 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Perspectives in Virology VIII 2/7-8/1972 [UNREADABLE] 2/2-3/1990, 1972-1990 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - PRC Trip Reunion Seminar, 6/6/1984 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Princeton Lipsome Conference, 4/29/1985-5/1/1985 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Purdue University 10/29/1970 Johns Hopkins 12/1970 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - R. Companes-Caspary Talk (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - R.U. Reunion, 6/6-9/1976 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Report of Public Health Grant NYC Annual Report, 1960-1961 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Rhabdovirus Conference, 6/15-18/1972 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Rhabdovirus Meeting, 7/4-7/1979, 7/14-16/1982 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Roche Institute Seminar, 10/7/1971 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Roos, 1 of 2 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Roos, 2 of 2 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Rous Anniversary Lecture, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Royal Society, 6/29/1986 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - RSM Meeting on Infectious Diseases, 1903-1985 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Rutgers Symposium (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - SI Morse Lecture, 5/24/1982 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - SAB Abstract 1961 ASCI 1960, 1960-1961 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Scientific American, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Seale Laboratories, 7/23-24/1974 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Seminar Albany Medical College, 3/1/1978 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Seminar Albert Einstein, 4/3/1974 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Seminar NY Medical College, 4/3/1978 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Seminar PA State University, 5/9/1983 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Seminar University of California Irvine 2/0/1978 & UCLA 2/9/1978 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Seminars, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Seminars, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - 2nd International Congress of Virology, 6/27/1971 7/3/1971 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - 2nd International Workshop Puerto Rico, 6/1/1980 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Science Writers Visit, 11/16/1977 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Scripps Scientific Review Committee, 1983-1985 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - 6th International Congress of Virology Japan, 9/1-7/1984 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Sloan Kettering Course, 1/4/1978 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Sloan Viruses Conference, 12/7-8/1968 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Society for General Microbiology, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Southwestern Medical Dallas, 4/7-8/1982 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - St. Jude Seminar, 3/26/1971 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Medical Program Caspary & Cornell, 4/20/1981, 4/23/1981 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Symposium on SSPE Beirut Lebanon, 11/4-6/1982 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Symposium on SSPE Milan Italy, 5/22/1985 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Swine Influenza Meeting, 2/20/1976 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Talk LAB, SKI, NYU, DMC, 1967 February-March (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Thesis Talks Merz, Peluso, Silver, 1970-1979 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Toronto XI International Congress of Biochemistry, 7/8-14/1979 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Treponemas Workshop, 10/15/1971 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - US-EMBO Meeting (England), 1/27-31/1978; 1 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - US-EMBO Meeting (England), 1/27-30/1978; 2 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - US-USSR Influenza Symposium, 5/23/1978 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - UCLA Symposium Keystone Colorado, 4/1985 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - University of Chicago, 10/10/1973 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - University of Cologne Meeting, 11/1-4/1983 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - University of Connecticut 10/1/1973 Louisiana State University 11/30/1973 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - University of Minnesota Infectious Disease Series, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - University of Pennsylvania Seminar, 1/20/1972 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - University of Tennessee, 5/18/1972 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - University of Toronto, 3/4/1971 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - University of Western Ontario Seminar, 5/3/1978 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - University of Wisconsin Seminar, 3/19/1973 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Vaccine & Serum Production Organization, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Viral Immunopathology Symposium San Diego, 10/26-30/1980 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Virology Study Section, 1/1976 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Virology Study Section, 9/25-27/1975 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Virus Attachment & Entry Symposium, 4/10-13/1985 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Washington University 2/19/1968 Einstein Seminar 1/9/1968 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Wednesday Seminar 4/9/1958 & 1959 SAB (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Wed. Talk 1964 Federation 1964 Roswell Park 1964 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Wed. Talk 1966 ASM 1966 PHRI 1966 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Weinstein Lecture Tufts, 3/16/1984 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Winston Institute 10/15/1968 LAB Seminar 11/7/1968 Princeton Conference 11/11-12/1968 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Markey Scholars Program, 1983-1986; 2
  - Markey Foundation Meetings, 1984-1986; 1 of 2 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Markey Foundation Meetings, 1984-1986; 2 of 2 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Markey Scholars Award, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Markey Scholars Award Program, 1985; 1 of 2 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Markey Scholars Award Program, 1985; 2 of 2 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Markey Scholars Award Program Applications (RU), 1984-1985 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Markey Scholars Award Program Correspondence, 1904-1986; 1 of 2 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Markey Scholars Award Program Correspondence, 1984-1986; 2 of 2 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Markey Scholars Award Program Drafts of Brochure, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Markey PhD Training Grant, 1983-1984 (Box 29, Folder 4)